<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Polyteknisk Radiogruppe</title><link>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Polyteknisk Radiogruppe</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2021 Polyteknisk Radiogruppe</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Meet the PRG the 15th and 16th of february</title><link>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/blog/2022-02-10-prg-in-the-student-fair/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/blog/2022-02-10-prg-in-the-student-fair/</guid><description>The Radiogrouppe wil be presented to the students in the DSE PF student fair. We are going to show a demonstration of Music for oscilloscopes, showing the arcade machine and also some radio experiment. We are exited to present the association to all the new students. The event is organized by PF and DSE.
PF and DSE would like to invite you for our Study Fair. During the fair, you will have the opportunity to meet associations, organizations and clubs at DTU.</description></item><item><title>How to add new content to PRG webpage</title><link>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/blog/2021-12-15-add-new-content/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/blog/2021-12-15-add-new-content/</guid><description>This is a copy of the content of the file readme.md from the repository of the webpage on github. It explains how to add new content to the PRG webpage.
PRG-web This repository is the webpage of the Polyteknisk Radiogruppe part of Technical University of Denmark placed in Copenhagen. This webpage is created with gohugo, Markdown and HTML/CSS.
Gohugo, or Hugo, is a framework for building static websites. It makes easy to add new content to a new webpage.</description></item><item><title>PRG launch his new website</title><link>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/blog/2021-11-20-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/blog/2021-11-20-first-post/</guid><description>We are launching a new website with updated information about our radiogrouppe.
PRG is a club for all DTU students interested in HAM radio communication and electronics. The club is located at DTU building 101 E, 1 floor, room 116C. We have a club day every Wednesday at 17:30, where you can meet a board member who can help you sign into the club. The price for membership pr semester is 60kr.</description></item><item><title>Arduino Day - Introduction to Arduino</title><link>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/activities/2022-03-23-arduino-day-introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/activities/2022-03-23-arduino-day-introduction/</guid><description>DESCRIPTION Celebrate the Arduino Day with an introduction of this amazing board in the Polyteknisk Radiogruppe (PRG). It is going to be an introduction workshop, perfect for the people that want to start in this world of electronics, but also more experienced people are welcome to the event to have fun time and share their knowledge.
Link of the facebook event
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO TALK ABOUT? We are going to give an introduction about what is arduino, what can we do with this board, some theoretical part, and then&amp;hellip; hands on with the board and let see what we get.</description></item><item><title>Restarting the club</title><link>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/activities/2022-03-07-restarting-the-club/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/activities/2022-03-07-restarting-the-club/</guid><description>DESCRIPTION After 2.5 years of moving the club from the basement up to our new rooms on the 1.s floor and due to COVID-19, we are now ready to open the club for all members. Thus, on the 16th of March at 18:00 we will officially open the club for all PRG&amp;rsquo;s members. Therefore, you are invited to come by and say hello and chill.
All students at DTU, should now have access to the 1 floor and PRG&amp;rsquo;s room via their student cards.</description></item><item><title>Study Fair - Studiemesse by PF and DSE</title><link>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/activities/2022-02-15-pf-dse-fair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/activities/2022-02-15-pf-dse-fair/</guid><description>DESCRIPTION The Radiogrouppe will be presented presented to the students in the DSE PF student fair. Come to visit us at the S-Huset!
PF and DSE would like to invite you for our Study Fair. During the fair, you will have the opportunity to meet associations, organizations and clubs at DTU. This event will give you insight into what you can do in your free time and what you can gain by being part of different organizations.</description></item><item><title>Study Fair - Studiemesse by PF and DSE</title><link>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/activities/2022-02-16-pf-dse-fair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://polyteknisk-radiogruppe.github.io/activities/2022-02-16-pf-dse-fair/</guid><description>DESCRIPTION The Radiogrouppe will be presented to the students in the DSE PF student fair. Come to visit us at the S-Huset!
PF and DSE would like to invite you for our Study Fair. During the fair, you will have the opportunity to meet associations, organizations and clubs at DTU. This event will give you insight into what you can do in your free time and what you can gain by being part of different organizations.</description></item></channel></rss>